basketwallpapers.com 2017-11-19

# Privacy Policy | Basketball Wallpapers at BasketWallpapers.com

**Your Personal Information:**  
BasketWallpapers.com does not require, collect or store personal information. This Web site is free for all and You can use it without need to register account and leave any personal information.  
Therefore Your privacy is 100% safe on our Web site.

**Third Party Advertising:**  
– We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to  
know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: [  
http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/).

**Third Party Cookies:**  
Third-party advertising companies like Google AdSense i mentioned above may place or recognize a unique "cookie" in your browser while serving advertisements during Your visits. Cookies are not harmful in any way to You or Your PC and can be removed directly in any modern Web browser with no need of any anti-virus or anti-spyware software.

**External Links:**  
This site contains links to other sites including but not limited to:  
1\. Sites of designers who made some of wallpapers appearing on this site.  
2\. Advertising Web sites.  
3\. Friendly sites and partners of BasketWallpapers.com  
BasketWallpapers.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any third-party Web sites.

**Contact:**  
If You have any questions or issues about BasketWallpapers.com privacy policy please feel free to use [Contact Page](http://www.basketwallpapers.com/contact/).
